tableplus.io 2019-06-07

# TablePlus | Modern, Native Tool for Database Management

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which TablePlus collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the https://tableplus.io/ website ("Site") and TablePlus app (“app”).

SECTION 1 - COLLECTION OF INFORMATION

On the app, we don’t collect personal information except the email you used to register for the license. We use Fabric to collect some anonymous, non-personal behavioural data when you use the app, including number of new users, active users and crash tracking.

On the website, we use Google Analytics to automatically collect certain kinds of non-personal information from you when you use the website, including device, browser type, operating system, referring or exit web pages, click patterns, Session ID, your computer's IP address, and some other browser-based information.

SECTION 2 - HOW YOUR INFORMATION IS USED

Except as provided herein, we collect and use your personal and non-personal information for internal purposes only or for gathering aggregate and anonymized data, and we do not sell, rent, or share personally identifiable information about you with other people or with nonaffiliated companies except as described below. We may use your information in the following ways:

To communicate with you about important announcements, special offers and support.

To provide you with and enhance the Services.

To gather generic product, location and other contributed information to make reports based on aggregate anonymized data, which we may use internally, or which we may share with others for a variety of purposes, including for their own uses.

To comply with court and governmental orders.

YOUR USER CONTENT

Your User Content will be treated as follows:

We never sync or send your database credentials, history, favorite or any your database content to any of our servers. The credentials are always being saved securely on your computer.

We will never send news, spam to your emails except important announcements, special offers and support.

SECTION 3 - CONSENT

How do you get my consent?

When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, place an order, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.

If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.

How do I withdraw my consent?

If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, by contacting us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

SECTION 4 - DISCLOSURE

We will not disclose your personal information unless we are required by law to do so or you violate our Terms of Service.

SECTION 5 - THIRD-PARTY SERVICES

In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.

However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.

For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.

In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located in a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.

As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.

Once you leave our website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.

Links

When you click on links on our website, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.

SECTION 6 - SECURITY

To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.

COOKIES

Our website may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

SECTION 7 - AGE OF CONSENT

By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.

SECTION 8 - CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.

If we sell assets or are acquired by or merged with another entity, we may provide such entity customer information without obtaining your further consent. We may provide notice of such asset sales, acquisitions, or mergers on the Site.

QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION

If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Last updated on Oct 26, 2018
